dress.ph 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy - dress.ph

We respect the privacy rights of its online visitors ("you", "your", "yours") and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We have adopted a corporate wide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information that you provide us with. As part of our commitment to your privacy rights and security, our website has been certified by Cybertt.

The following information is provided by Dress.ph to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By visiting Dress.ph you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Dress.ph's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with Dress.ph.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link and Dress.ph is not responsible for any personal information you submit to third parties via our website. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organizations before submitting your details.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND HOW?

Dress.ph collects personal information in several ways when you place an order, buy a gift voucher for a friend or register for a service offered by Dress.ph. By registering, you are consenting to the collection of your personal data. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and credit/debit card billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfill your order.

Saved card details will never be shared with third parties and will only be used to process your order, using our payment partner's systems. Additionally we may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

Users of Dress.phTV will only have their name and email address processed in order to provide the service and respond to any complaints or otherwise where required by law on in connection with any legal proceedings or dispute.

WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?

Our site uses cookies (very small files that are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you visit our site in future.

There are four types of cookies:

Website functionality cookies

These cookies enable you to browse the website and use our features such as shopping baskets and wish lists

Website analytics cookies

We use these cookies to measure and analyse how our customers use the website. This allows us to continuously improve our website and your shopping experience.

Customer preference cookies

When browsing or shopping online, the website will remember preferences you make (for example your user name, language or location). This makes your browsing experience simpler, easier and more personal to you.

Targeting cookies or advertising cookies

These cookies are used to deliver adverts relevant to you. In addition, they limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as helping us measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

By using our website you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device and access them when you visit the site in the future.

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.

Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available atwww.AboutCookies.org. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.
